carfolio.com 2011-11-20

# Carfolio.com Privacy Policy

## BMW reveals latest 3 Series

Today BMW released information on their latest 3 Series range, which carries the model designation F30. Initially available as a 4 door saloon with 4 engine choices, the range is sure to be expanded with more diesel and petrol engine choices, all-wheel drive variants, and of course, the obligatory station wagon (likely to still be called Touring), coupé and convertible versions, as well as the usual raft of powerful M-badged range-toppers. 

More...

## 2011 Kia Rio

Details of [Kia](http://www.carfolio.com/specifications/models/?man=3303)'s latest 5 door Rio hatchbacks have been released ahead of the launch of the 3 door Kia Rio models which will take place in September of 2011, at the IAA in Frankfurt. Kia's revised Rio has been styled by a team led by Peter Schreyer. 

More...

## Ginetta Cars Launches G40R

Ginetta Cars have been producing racing cars and light, agile sports cars for decades. Started by the Walklett brothers, Bob, Douglas, Ivor and Trevor in the 1950s, the company has survived and have launched their most recent road car - the [Ginetta G40R](http://www.carfolio.com/specifications/models/car/?car=250910). 

More...

## The 2012 Chevrolet Camaro ZL1 - Most powerful Camaro ever

_All the following information and specifications are preliminary, as Chevrolet have not yet released complete and final specifications._ [Chevrolet](http://www.carfolio.com/specifications/models/?man=1276)'s 2012 model year [**Camaro ZL1**](http://www.carfolio.com/specifications/models/car/?car=233068) is the most powerful [Chevrolet Camaro](http://www.carfolio.com/search/results/?terms=chevrolet+camaro&num=250) yet. The 2+2 seater coupé features a 6.2 litre **supercharged** V8 (LSA) engine, powering the rear wheels via a 6 speed manual transmission. 

More...

## 2011 F10 BMW M5 specifications released

The specifications for the [2011 F10-series BMW M5](http://www.carfolio.com/specifications/models/car/?car=247181) have been released by BMW. The naturally aspirated 5-litre V10 of the previous [E60 BMW M5](http://www.carfolio.com/specifications/models/car/?car=120780) gives way to a turbocharged V8 of 4.4 litres capacity. 

More...

## New BMW 1 Series F20 details

The details of the latest model range of the 1 Series 5 door hatchback have been released by BMW. Other body styles, including a high-tailed hatchback similar in concept to the 5 Series GT are to follow soon. 

More...

## 1992 Nissan Skyline Autech - unique and rare

Autech, Nissan's own tuning arm, has produced a number of interesting limited production models based on regular Nissan vehicle underpinnings. In 1992, Autech produced and sold a very special version of the then-current Nissan R32 Skyline range. 

More...

## McLaren release final MP4-12C technical specifications

McLaren have amended the published technical specifications of their latest model, the [McLaren MP4-12C](http://www.carfolio.com/specifications/models/car/?car=219549), prior to its general release. Driving reviews are to be published all over the automotive world tomorrow, when the February 14th embargo lifts, so we are publishing their latest specifications for you here. 

More...

## Nissan beefs up GT-R for 2011

Nissan have updated their "Godzilla" - the [R35 Nissan GT-R](http://www.carfolio.com/specifications/models/car/?car=220319). Available in Japan from 17 November 2010, the 2011 model year R35 Nissan GT-R features _more power_. 

More...

See all articles

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at webmaster@carfolio.com. 

At Carfolio.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by Carfolio.com and how it is used. 

## Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers, we may make use of log files. This could include internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track movement on the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information in any way. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

The only time Carfolio.com will set or query users' browser cookies is for the functionality of the "Your Stable" section of the site, where the Carfolio.com ID numbers of the models the user chooses to add to that section of the site are stored via cookies. No personal information is stored or retrieved by Carfolio.com at any time. 

Carfolio.com partners with Google AdSense and Amazon.co.uk for serving advertisements to users, and these 3rd party services may make use of cookies to track user clicks. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on Carfolio.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies or JavaScript) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

Carfolio.com has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for Google AdSense and Amazon.co.uk to set cookies for advertising. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Carfolio.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such 3rd party advertisers and web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
